http://www.stmarks.net/privacy-policy/

Get the complete 2020 Advent and Christmas Schedule…then join us!
Details »
Mouse over and click these words to see the full post for days and times. Bookmark the link. Download a hard copy if you’d like.
Better yet, your Daily Email from St. Mark’s will provide links to all of these virtual events, as well as other opportunities to connect for fellowship, prayer, centering, and worship. Mouse over and click these words to sign up, if you aren’t yet on the list!
All are welcome! We hope you’ll join us.
Calendar
Donate or Pledge
Member Login
Services & Location
AboutWho we areLeadership and GovernanceClergy and StaffParish LeadershipProgram LeadershipAltar GuildWorship CommitteeBylaws, Vestry Minutes, Annual ReportsForms and ProceduresHistoryMusicOur BuildingAppointments to Visit the NaveReserve Our FacilityEpiscopal Diocese of WashingtonServicesTimes & LocationSunday at St. Mark’sWorship ExperiencesService Bulletins & AnnouncementsSermonsChildren’s ChapelSunday SchoolNursery CareHospitalityThursday EucharistBaptismsMemorialsWeddingsSt. Mark’s CommunityWhat’s HappeningGroupsCare & CaregivingMusicChoirsConcerts | EventsMusic StudioVisual ArtsDance StudioMeditation CenterSt. Mark’s PlayersYoga CenterParish ResourcesBylaws, Vestry Minutes, Annual ReportsForms and ProceduresDonate or PledgeLeadership and GovernanceLearningChristian EducationCatechesis | Level 1SermonsVerna J. Dozier Memorial LibraryLife and Ministry of Verna DozierIntroduction to the CollectionUsing the Online CatalogRacial Justice Books SurveyGet InvolvedNewcomers and VisitorsBelonging ClassJoin Our CommunityBecome a MemberVolunteer at St. Mark’sDonate or PledgeAnnual Pledge Form for the Year 2021Service & JusticeOutreach OverviewLocal OutreachEveryone Home DCFood Rescue USGreater DC Diaper BankIncarceration JusticeRefugee Resettlement ProgramSalvation Army Grate PatrolSamaritan Ministry of Greater WashingtonSunday SuppersWashington Interfaith Network (WIN)International OutreachHonduras OutreachMid-East Working GroupEco-JusticePreventing Gun ViolenceYouth OutreachYouth & Family MinistriesChildren’s ChapelService Trips and ProjectsSunday School
Sundays Online
10:00am Eucharist FB Live
11:00am Virtual Coffee Hour Zoom
12:00pm Sermon Seminar Zoom
5:00pm Contemplative Eucharist Zoom
GET DETAILS TO CONNECT
Location
St. Mark’s Episcopal Church
301 A Street, SE
Washington, DC 20003
GET DIRECTIONS
Privacy Policy
We greatly value the trust you place in us. Please know that the personal information you provide us with will not be given to or shared with anyone outside of St. Marks Episcopal Church, Capitol Hill.
Our Mailing Lists
St. Marks is the sole owner of any information collected on our website and we do not sell or distribute this information. The personal information you provide us (name, address, email, phone number, etc.) is retained in our records for use only by and within the St. Mark’s community. This information is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by authorized staff members. When you sign up for our mailing lists, you can expect to receive only St. Marks or St. Marks-related information which is in line with our mission. Any mailing which we produce in cooperation with a partner organization will include only St. Marks material. Constant Contact is used to send email newsletters and other important updates to church members and others who have asked to receive information and updates by email.
How does St. Mark’s use my email address?
Your email address is used to create and identify your account on stmarks.net. Your email address is also used by St. Mark’s to correspond with you about requests or sign-ups you may have submitted or to keep you updated if you opt-in to receive emails from us. We may also use your email address to notify you about important changes to our website. If you would rather not receive this information or would like to opt-out of receiving email of this kind, simply click on the “unsubscribe” link that appears on the bottom of any email from stmarks.net and follow the simple instructions to have your email address removed.
Cookies
To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies” or similar technologies on our site. Cookies are text files placed in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information; however, once you choose to furnish a site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our site (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to the website), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use payment portals on our site. We may also use cookies to help offer you products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you. We do not track where you go on the world wide web.
You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered at stmarks.net. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.
Your Consent
You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms of service, and you agree that using this site signifies your consent to the St. Marks’s Privacy Policy. St Marks reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this privacy policy, at any time without advance notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Questions?
If you have any questions about the St. Marks Privacy Policy or the way we collect and use information, please contact us at parishadmin@stmarks.net or call us at 202.543.0053.
Contact Us
Like us on Facebook
Follow on Twitter
Subscribe to Emails
Reserve our Facility
MemberLogin
Church of the Open Communion
© St. Mark’s Episcopal Church
